## YU HONG KENNARD KWAN

+85268747345 | Kennard2101@gmail.com

## **Qualification Profile**

An energetic and highly-focused professional with master's degree in Geomatics (GIS) and excellent educational credentials and experience in GIS and IoT projects. Remarkable talent and knowledge in analysing information, collaborating with clients, and providing support to GIS Analysts. Analytical planner adept at identifying and isolating GIS challenges, as well as devising solutions to resolutely mitigate issues. Articulate and refined communicator with fluency in Cantonese, English, and Mandarin Chinese as well as conservational command over Japanese.

#### **CORE PROFICIENCIES**

Project Planning & Assistance | GIS | Remote Sensing | Time Management | Operational Excellence

Microsoft Office | AUTOCAD | Adobe Illustrator | ArcGIS Pro/QGIS | ArcGIS Survey 123 | Python | Attention to Detail

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# City Connect Company Limited Project Coordinator

Sep 2021 to Present

- Provide assistance and coordination between different stakeholders in a GIS + IoT project for timely completion.
- Improve and gain hands-on experience on GIS by efficiently working on different projects.
- Data analysis and prepare progress reports for the project along with maps production.

Substance Lab Limited (December 2020 – March 2021) | (July 2019 – September 2019) | (September 2018 – February 2019) Intern

- Organised desktop research and performed a site inspection, interview, and analysis by expertly using ArcGIS Online and Survey 123 during the study.
- Conducted research and developed a conservation management plan for a declared monument.
- Provided assistance in heritage interpretation work for the revitalisation of heritage sites as per needs.
- Collected relevant information and created site inspection reports for declared monuments in Hong Kong.

## The Jockey Club CPS Limited Part-Time Associate

Oct 2018 to Oct 2020

- art Time 7.0500late
- Delivered exceptional services to ensure the smooth running of daily operations of Tai Kwun.
- Supported and responded to queries from visitors by providing immediate assistance to any contingency.
- Enhanced precious experience in customer service and communication.

#### **EDUCATION**

MSc Geomatics (GIS) Credit: The Polytechnic University of Hong Kong, 2022

BA (Conservation) Second Class Honours Division One: The University of Hong Kong, 2020

(Dean's Honour's List 2019 - 2020)

\_\_\_\_\_

Osaka University Short-term Student Exchange Program, Osaka University, 2018 Hong Kong Diploma of Secondary Education, St. Stephen's College, 2015